<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>PORTFOLIO on Zhizhuo Zhang</title>
    <link>https://ZhizhuoUp.github.io/portfolio/</link>
    <description>Recent content in PORTFOLIO on Zhizhuo Zhang</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>© Zhizhuo Zhang</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 02 May 2019 19:47:09 +0200</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://ZhizhuoUp.github.io/portfolio/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Knolling bot</title>
      <link>https://ZhizhuoUp.github.io/portfolio/knolling_bot/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 May 2019 19:47:09 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ZhizhuoUp.github.io/portfolio/knolling_bot/</guid>
      <description>Knolling bot</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Apple Picking Robotics Arm Control System Based on ROS</title>
      <link>https://ZhizhuoUp.github.io/portfolio/robot_arm_rrt/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ZhizhuoUp.github.io/portfolio/robot_arm_rrt/</guid>
      <description>This project aimed to develop a motion planning software package for a six-axis manipulator with Rapidly-Exploring Random Tree (RRT) algorithm as the core, which can theoretically be applicable to almost all six-axis robotic arms.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Evolving Soft Robots</title>
      <link>https://ZhizhuoUp.github.io/portfolio/evolving_soft_robot/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ZhizhuoUp.github.io/portfolio/evolving_soft_robot/</guid>
      <description>This project aims to evolve a soft robot with variable morphology and select the individual with the highest speed in a customized physical simulator by using evolutionary algorithm.
Develop a 3D Physics Simulator In general, the robot in a physical simulator can be defined as several masses and springs connected between each mass. Different physical parameters of each spring and each mass can affect the shape and movement of the robot.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Robotic Pick and Place Task Based on Visual Affordance Model</title>
      <link>https://ZhizhuoUp.github.io/portfolio/pick_and_place/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ZhizhuoUp.github.io/portfolio/pick_and_place/</guid>
      <description>In this project, I implemented the pick and place tasks in an environment with multiple objects. The robot arm can recognize objects it wants to grasp in a messy environment and try to grasp them with appropriate postures. After than, the robot arm can avoid obstcales during moving and place objects inside the box.
The whole task can be divided into several steps:
Human Demonstration Considering this task only include top-down grasping, where the pose of the gripper is reduced to three degrees of freedom (2D translation and 1D rotation) Therefore, the transnational degrees of freedom are naturally encoded in the 2D pixel coordinates.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
